KAMLESH PRAJAPATI

FRONT-END
WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a Front-End Developer with experience in developing in HTML5,CSS3, JavaScript and React. With over 2 years in a Retail supervisor background, I bring collaborative, communicative, problem solving traits, that allow me to develop strong web applications.

SKILLS









HTML

CSS

SASS

JavaScript









React

Jquery

ry BootStap

Git









GitHub REST API'S Firebase Responsive

Problem-solving | Leadership | Communication | Teamwork

CONTACT INFORMATION

Cell: 647 - 783 - 4030

Email: Kamlesh.prajapati62@gmail.com

Portfolio: <u>devkamlesh.com</u> Linkedin: <u>kamlesh-prajapati</u> GitHub: <u>Kamlesh-62</u>

PROJECT

FoodHub LIVE | GITHUB

Explore Thousand of cuisine recipes by searching food name. Moreover, Create your own recipe and post on website, so other user can take advantages of your Recipe.

HTML | SASS | REACT | FIREBASE | API'S

NEWS LIVE | GITHUB

The News website, where you can find world Top stories news. You can search your choice news to read, Moreover i have built dropdown menu to select your choice categories news. Also Covid-19 cases data available. I have used two API's to build this website.

HTML | SASS | API'S | ES6 JAVASCRIPT

EDUCATION

JUNO COLLEGE, Bootcamp (2021)

- Immersive Web Development Certificate
- Accelerated JavaScript
- Accelerated Web Development

HUMBER COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY (2019 - 2020)

- -In business accounting analyzing financial information on business activity,
- -recording transactions, and producing financial statements.
- -include bookkeeping, preparing and filing tax returns, and drafting financial reports.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Store Supervisor

Action Convenience (2019 - Present)

- -Assign sales workers to duties and prepare work schedules
- Resolve problems that arise, such as customer complaints and supply shortages
- Maintain specified inventory and order merchandise

Credit Officer

HDFC LTD (2018 - 2019)

- Calculation of Net Present Values of maturing assets
- Cash flow method of assessment of NRI Loans, Ability to assess a Salaried Loan
- interpretation of Credit Bureau Report, Assessment of Income, Analysis of Bank Statements, Assessing eligibility